<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>MoneySkillTalk Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/</link>
    <atom:link href="/en/rss2.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    
    <description>Learn how to make the most of your money skill here.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:51:27 GMT</pubDate>
    <generator>http://hexo.io/</generator>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Advertise on the TaiwanTalk Korean Community Website</title>
      <link>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/global-korean-online-community-taiwantalk/</link>
      <guid>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/global-korean-online-community-taiwantalk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        Most visitors to TaiwanTalk are Koreans or Korean speakers living in Taiwan, either short-term or long-term. If your product or service is related to Taiwan, you can run more targeted ads aimed at this specific audience.
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>TaiwanTalk</strong> is an online community for Koreans living in or interested in Taiwan, as well as foreigners who speak Korean.</p><p>It’s a platform for sharing practical information and experiences related to life in Taiwan, actively used by Korean students, expatriates, travelers, immigrants, and working holiday visa holders currently residing in Taiwan.</p><ul><li>Visit TaiwanTalk: <a href="https://www.taiwantalk.net/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.taiwantalk.net/</a></li></ul><hr><h2 id="Key-Features-of-TaiwanTalk"><a href="#Key-Features-of-TaiwanTalk" class="headerlink" title="Key Features of TaiwanTalk"></a>Key Features of TaiwanTalk</h2><ol><li><p><strong>Sharing Information About Life in Taiwan</strong>  </p><ul><li>Visa, ARC (Alien Resident Certificate), health insurance, banking, mobile phone setup, transportation, etc.  </li><li>Well-organized tips and guides for newcomers</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Region-Based Community</strong>  </p><ul><li>Local boards and groups for major cities like Taipei, Taichung, Kaohsiung  </li><li>Active sharing of regional info and meetup posts</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Study Abroad &amp; Working Holiday Info</strong>  </p><ul><li>University admissions, language study, exchange programs, scholarship opportunities  </li><li>Active discussions among students and WH visa holders</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Marketplace &amp; Job Board</strong>  </p><ul><li>Job listings from Korean businesses, restaurants, cafés, and academies  </li><li>Buy/sell used electronics, furniture, housing, travel tickets, etc.</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Culture &amp; Community Activities</strong>  </p><ul><li>Korean food, cultural events, Hallyu (K-culture) updates  </li><li>Discussions on dating or marrying Taiwanese and cross-cultural communication</li></ul></li></ol><hr><h2 id="How-to-Advertise-on-TaiwanTalk"><a href="#How-to-Advertise-on-TaiwanTalk" class="headerlink" title="How to Advertise on TaiwanTalk"></a>How to Advertise on TaiwanTalk</h2><p>Most TaiwanTalk users are Koreans or Korean speakers living in Taiwan, either short-term or long-term.<br>If your product or service is related to Taiwan, you can run highly targeted ads to this specific audience.</p><p>All advertisement posts are optimized for search engines, allowing them to be effectively exposed via Google, Naver, and more.</p><ul><li>TaiwanTalk Advertising Info: <a href="https://www.taiwantalk.net/advertising/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.taiwantalk.net/advertising/</a></li></ul><p>For advertising inquiries, contact us via email ( <a href="mailto:hello@globaltalk.asia" target="_blank" rel="noopener">hello@globaltalk.asia</a> ) or KakaoTalk ( <a href="http://www.taiwantalk.net/kakao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.taiwantalk.net/kakao/</a> ).</p>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/global-korean-online-community-taiwantalk/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Advertise on the JapanTalk Korean Community Website</title>
      <link>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/global-korean-online-community-japantalk/</link>
      <guid>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/global-korean-online-community-japantalk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        Most visitors to JapanTalk are Koreans or Korean speakers living in Japan, either short-term or long-term. If your product or service is related to Japan, you can run more targeted advertisements for this specific audience.
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>JapanTalk</strong> is an online community for Koreans living in or interested in Japan, as well as foreigners who speak Korean.</p><p>It’s a space for sharing useful information and experiences needed for daily life in Japan. The community is mainly used by Korean students, expatriates, travelers, immigrants, and working holiday visa holders living in Japan.</p><ul><li>Visit JapanTalk: <a href="https://www.japantalk.net/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.japantalk.net/</a></li></ul><hr><h2 id="Key-Features-of-JapanTalk"><a href="#Key-Features-of-JapanTalk" class="headerlink" title="Key Features of JapanTalk"></a>Key Features of JapanTalk</h2><ol><li><p><strong>Sharing Information About Life in Japan</strong>  </p><ul><li>Visa, banking, mobile phone setup, transportation tips, etc.  </li><li>Well-organized tips and guidance for newcomers settling in</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Region-Based Community</strong>  </p><ul><li>Sub-groups and boards for major cities like Tokyo, Osaka, Nagoya, Kyoto, Fukuoka, Sapporo, etc.  </li><li>Active sharing of local info and meetups</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Study Abroad &amp; Working Holiday Info</strong>  </p><ul><li>University admission, language programs, exchange programs, scholarships  </li><li>Active discussions among students and sharing of WH experiences</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Marketplace &amp; Job Board</strong>  </p><ul><li>Job postings from Korean companies, Korean restaurants, cafés, academies, etc.  </li><li>Buy/sell used electronics, furniture, rooms, attraction tickets, and more</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Culture &amp; Community Activities</strong>  </p><ul><li>Korean food, cultural events, K-culture updates  </li><li>Stories about dating or marrying Japanese partners, and cultural exchange</li></ul></li></ol><hr><h2 id="How-to-Advertise-on-JapanTalk"><a href="#How-to-Advertise-on-JapanTalk" class="headerlink" title="How to Advertise on JapanTalk"></a>How to Advertise on JapanTalk</h2><p>Most visitors to JapanTalk are Koreans or Korean speakers living in Japan short-term or long-term.<br>If your product or service is related to Japan, you can run targeted advertisements for this audience.</p><p>In addition, all ad posts are optimized for search engines, ensuring effective exposure on Google, Naver, and more.</p><ul><li>JapanTalk Advertising Info: <a href="https://www.japantalk.net/advertising/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.japantalk.net/advertising/</a></li></ul><p>For advertising inquiries, contact us via email ( <a href="mailto:hello@japantalk.net" target="_blank" rel="noopener">hello@japantalk.net</a> ) or KakaoTalk ( <a href="http://www.japantalk.net/kakao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.japantalk.net/kakao/</a> ).</p>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/global-korean-online-community-japantalk/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Advertise on the ChinaTalk Korean Community Website</title>
      <link>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/global-korean-online-community-chinatalk/</link>
      <guid>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/global-korean-online-community-chinatalk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        The main visitors to ChinaTalk are Koreans or Korean speakers living in China, either short-term or long-term. If your product or service is related to China, you can run more targeted advertisements toward this specific audience.
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>ChinaTalk</strong> is an online community for Koreans living in or interested in China, as well as foreigners who speak Korean.</p><p>It’s a place to share useful information and experiences about life in China, actively used by Korean students, expatriates, travelers, and immigrants currently residing in China.</p><ul><li>Visit ChinaTalk: <a href="https://www.chinatalk.net/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.chinatalk.net/</a></li></ul><hr><h2 id="Key-Features-of-ChinaTalk"><a href="#Key-Features-of-ChinaTalk" class="headerlink" title="Key Features of ChinaTalk"></a>Key Features of ChinaTalk</h2><ol><li><p><strong>Sharing Information About Life in China</strong></p><ul><li>Visa, banking, mobile phone setup, transportation tips, etc.</li><li>Well-organized guides for those settling in China for the first time</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Region-Based Community</strong></p><ul><li>Sub-groups and boards for major cities like Beijing, Shanghai, Guangzhou, Shenzhen, Hangzhou, etc.</li><li>Active sharing of local information and meetups</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Study Abroad &amp; Working Holiday Info</strong></p><ul><li>Info about Chinese universities, language programs, exchange programs, scholarships, etc.</li><li>Active discussions among students, including working holiday experiences</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Marketplace &amp; Job Board</strong></p><ul><li>Job postings from Korean companies, restaurants, cafes, academies, etc.</li><li>Buy/sell second-hand electronics, furniture, rooms, attraction tickets, and more</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Culture &amp; Community Activities</strong></p><ul><li>Korean food, cultural events, and K-culture news</li><li>Discussions about dating/marriage with Chinese partners and cultural differences</li></ul></li></ol><hr><h2 id="How-to-Advertise-on-ChinaTalk"><a href="#How-to-Advertise-on-ChinaTalk" class="headerlink" title="How to Advertise on ChinaTalk"></a>How to Advertise on ChinaTalk</h2><p>Most visitors to ChinaTalk are Koreans or Korean speakers living in China, either short-term or long-term.<br>If your product or service is related to China, you can run targeted ads aimed at this audience.</p><p>In addition, all ad posts are SEO-optimized to be effectively exposed to search engines like Google and Naver.</p><ul><li>ChinaTalk Advertising Information: <a href="https://www.chinatalk.net/advertising/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.chinatalk.net/advertising/</a></li></ul><p>For inquiries about advertising, please contact us via email ( <a href="mailto:hello@chinatalk.net" target="_blank" rel="noopener">hello@chinatalk.net</a> ) or KakaoTalk ( <a href="http://www.chinatalk.net/kakao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.chinatalk.net/kakao/</a> ).</p>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/global-korean-online-community-chinatalk/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Advertise on the USATalk Korean Community Website</title>
      <link>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/global-korean-online-community-usatalk/</link>
      <guid>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/global-korean-online-community-usatalk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        Most visitors to USATalk are Koreans or Korean speakers living in the United States, either short-term or long-term. If your product or service is related to the U.S., you can run highly targeted ads aimed at this audience.
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>USATalk</strong> is an online community for Koreans living in or interested in the United States, as well as foreigners who speak Korean.</p><p>It is a space for sharing useful information and experiences about life in the U.S., primarily used by Korean students, expatriates, travelers, and immigrants currently living in the country.</p><ul><li>Visit USATalk: <a href="https://www.usatalk.net/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.usatalk.net/</a></li></ul><hr><h2 id="Key-Features-of-USATalk"><a href="#Key-Features-of-USATalk" class="headerlink" title="Key Features of USATalk"></a>Key Features of USATalk</h2><ol><li><p><strong>Sharing Information About Life in the U.S.</strong>  </p><ul><li>Visas, banking, mobile phone setup, transportation, etc.  </li><li>Well-organized tips and guides for newcomers</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Region-Based Community</strong>  </p><ul><li>Sub-groups and boards for major cities like New York, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Seattle, Washington DC, Chicago, etc.  </li><li>Active sharing of local info and meetups</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Study Abroad &amp; Working Holiday Info</strong>  </p><ul><li>U.S. university admissions, language programs, exchange programs, scholarships  </li><li>Active student discussions and working holiday experiences</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Marketplace &amp; Job Board</strong>  </p><ul><li>Job postings from Korean businesses, restaurants, cafés, academies, etc.  </li><li>Buy/sell secondhand electronics, furniture, rooms, attraction tickets, and more</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Culture &amp; Community Activities</strong>  </p><ul><li>Korean food, cultural events, K-culture news  </li><li>Stories about dating/marrying Americans and navigating cultural differences</li></ul></li></ol><hr><h2 id="How-to-Advertise-on-USATalk"><a href="#How-to-Advertise-on-USATalk" class="headerlink" title="How to Advertise on USATalk"></a>How to Advertise on USATalk</h2><p>Most visitors to USATalk are Koreans or Korean speakers living in the U.S., either short-term or long-term.<br>If your product or service is related to the U.S., you can run highly targeted ads toward this audience.</p><p>In addition, ad posts are SEO-optimized for effective exposure on Google, Naver, and other search engines.</p><ul><li>USATalk Advertising Info: <a href="https://www.usatalk.net/advertising/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.usatalk.net/advertising/</a></li></ul><p>For inquiries, contact us via email ( <a href="mailto:hello@globaltalk.asia" target="_blank" rel="noopener">hello@globaltalk.asia</a> ) or KakaoTalk ( <a href="http://www.usatalk.net/kakao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.usatalk.net/kakao/</a> ).</p>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/global-korean-online-community-usatalk/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Advertise on the VietnamTalk Korean Community Website</title>
      <link>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/global-korean-online-community-vietnamtalk/</link>
      <guid>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/global-korean-online-community-vietnamtalk/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        Most visitors to VietnamTalk are Koreans or Korean speakers living in Vietnam, either short-term or long-term. If your product or service is related to Vietnam, you can run more targeted ads aimed at this specific audience.
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>VietnamTalk</strong> is an online community for Koreans living in or interested in Vietnam, as well as foreigners who speak Korean.</p><p>It’s a space to share useful information and experiences about life in Vietnam, actively used by Korean students, expatriates, travelers, and immigrants currently residing in the country.</p><ul><li>Visit VietnamTalk: <a href="https://www.vietnamtalk.net/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.vietnamtalk.net/</a></li></ul><hr><h2 id="Key-Features-of-VietnamTalk"><a href="#Key-Features-of-VietnamTalk" class="headerlink" title="Key Features of VietnamTalk"></a>Key Features of VietnamTalk</h2><ol><li><p><strong>Sharing Information About Life in Vietnam</strong>  </p><ul><li>Visa, banking, mobile phone setup, transportation, etc.  </li><li>Well-organized tips and guides for those settling in</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Region-Based Community</strong>  </p><ul><li>City-specific groups and boards for Hanoi, Ho Chi Minh City, Da Nang, Hue, Nha Trang, etc.  </li><li>Active sharing of local information and meetups</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Study Abroad &amp; Working Holiday Info</strong>  </p><ul><li>University admissions in Vietnam, language courses, exchange programs, scholarships  </li><li>Lively communication among students, including WH experiences</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Marketplace &amp; Job Board</strong>  </p><ul><li>Job postings from Korean companies, Korean restaurants, cafés, academies, etc.  </li><li>Trade used electronics, furniture, rooms, attraction tickets, and more</li></ul></li><li><p><strong>Culture &amp; Community Activities</strong>  </p><ul><li>Korean food, cultural events, K-culture news  </li><li>Stories about dating/marriage with Vietnamese partners, and cultural differences</li></ul></li></ol><hr><h2 id="How-to-Advertise-on-VietnamTalk"><a href="#How-to-Advertise-on-VietnamTalk" class="headerlink" title="How to Advertise on VietnamTalk"></a>How to Advertise on VietnamTalk</h2><p>Most visitors to VietnamTalk are Koreans or Korean speakers living in Vietnam, either short-term or long-term.<br>If your product or service is related to Vietnam, you can run highly targeted ads aimed at this audience.</p><p>Additionally, ad posts are SEO-optimized to be effectively exposed on Google, Naver, and other search engines.</p><ul><li>VietnamTalk Advertising Info: <a href="https://www.vietnamtalk.net/advertising/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.vietnamtalk.net/advertising/</a></li></ul><p>For inquiries, contact us via email ( <a href="mailto:hello@vietnamtalk.net" target="_blank" rel="noopener">hello@vietnamtalk.net</a> ) or KakaoTalk ( <a href="http://www.vietnamtalk.net/kakao/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.vietnamtalk.net/kakao/</a> ).</p>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/global-korean-online-community-vietnamtalk/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Analytics - Check whether a website is built with WordPress and various information</title>
      <link>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/wordpress-wp-data-analytics/</link>
      <guid>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/wordpress-wp-data-analytics/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        WordPress Analytics is a free online tool that checks whether a website is built with WordPress and analyzes information such as the theme, plugins, and hosting service being used.
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WordPress Analytics (<a href="http://www.wp-data.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.wp-data.com</a>) is a free online tool that checks whether a website is built with WordPress and analyzes information such as the theme, plugins, and hosting service being used. It is especially useful for developers, designers, and marketers who want to understand the technology stack of competitors or reference websites.</p><p>🔍 Main Features<br>    1.    WordPress Detection<br>• Automatically detects if the entered URL is a WordPress website.<br>    2.    Theme &amp; Plugin Analysis<br>• Identifies and lists the WordPress themes and plugins used on the site.<br>    3.    Hosting Service Information<br>• Estimates and displays the site’s hosting provider.<br>    4.    Agency Info Registration<br>• Allows users to add or edit agency information shown in the analysis.<br>    5.    Multilingual Support<br>• Available in multiple languages including Korean, English, Japanese, Chinese, and Vietnamese.</p><p>🛠 How to Use<br>    1.    Visit <a href="http://www.wp-data.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.wp-data.com</a><br>    2.    Enter the URL of the website you want to analyze (e.g., <a href="https://example.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://example.com</a>)    3.    Click the “Analyze” button to view information such as WordPress usage, theme, plugins, and hosting.</p><p>🎯 Use Cases<br>• Understand the tech stack of reference sites and apply it to your own projects.<br>• Benchmark competitors by checking which themes and plugins they use.<br>• Manage your agency portfolio by registering your agency’s information.</p><p>WordPress Analytics (<a href="http://www.wp-data.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.wp-data.com</a>) is a simple and convenient tool that requires no installation or login. It is highly useful for quickly retrieving technical information about WordPress-based websites. However, since it is based on publicly available data, some plugins or customized elements may not be detected accurately.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/wordpress-wp-data-analytics/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Sale Now - Get the latest discounts and free promotions for WordPress themes, plugins, and hosting services</title>
      <link>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/wordpress-wp-sale-now/</link>
      <guid>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/wordpress-wp-sale-now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        WordPress Sale Now is a website that provides real-time updates on the latest discounts and free promotions for WordPress themes, plugins, and hosting services.
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WordPress Sale Now is a website that provides real-time updates on the latest discounts and free promotions for WordPress themes, plugins, and hosting services. It’s a useful platform for those building or running websites or online stores, as it allows users to quickly view a wide range of deals all in one place.</p><p>⸻</p><p>🔍 Key Features<br>    1.    Real-Time Discount Updates<br>WordPress Sale Now constantly updates information on discounted themes, plugins, and hosting services, helping users find active promotions and purchase items at lower prices.<br>    2.    Free Download Promotions<br>Some premium themes and plugins are offered for free for a limited time. These promotions help users save costs while still accessing high-quality WordPress items.<br>    3.    Popular Product Rankings<br>The site provides weekly rankings of the most popular themes and plugins, helping users choose items that are currently trending and widely used.<br>    4.    Multilingual Support<br>WordPress Sale Now supports multiple languages including Korean, English, Japanese, and Chinese, making it accessible to users worldwide.</p><p>⸻</p><p>🛍️ Sample Discounted Products<br>    •    The7 Theme: A versatile theme with various design and layout options, currently available at 40% off.<br>    •    Elementor Plugin: A drag-and-drop page builder plugin, now offered at a 10% discount.<br>    •    Bluehost Hosting: A hosting service optimized for WordPress with various promotions currently available.</p><p>⸻</p><p>✅ Tips for Use<br>    •    Check Regularly: As discounts and free promotions are time-limited, visit the site frequently to stay up to date.</p><p>⸻</p><p>WordPress Sale Now is a convenient platform that gathers and shares discounts for WordPress-related products. It’s especially useful for those running websites or online businesses—feel free to check it out!</p><h1 id="Visit-now-https-www-wpsalenow-com"><a href="#Visit-now-https-www-wpsalenow-com" class="headerlink" title="Visit now: https://www.wpsalenow.com/"></a>Visit now: <a href="https://www.wpsalenow.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.wpsalenow.com/</a></h1>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/wordpress-wp-sale-now/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Sites Random Viewer - Explore WordPress-built websites from around the world</title>
      <link>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/wordpress-wp-viewer/</link>
      <guid>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/wordpress-wp-viewer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        WordPress Sites Random Viewer is a web-based tool that allows you to explore WordPress-built websites from around the world at random.
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WordPress Sites Random Viewer (<a href="http://www.wp-viewer.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.wp-viewer.com</a>) is a web-based tool that allows you to explore WordPress-built websites from around the world at random. It’s a valuable resource for designers, developers, and marketers who want to quickly browse a wide range of WordPress site examples.</p><p>⸻</p><p>🔍 Key Features<br>    •    Random Site Browsing: Simply click the “Next” button to discover various WordPress websites randomly.<br>    •    Simple Interface: With just a click, you can browse new sites without any complicated setup, making it very user-friendly.<br>    •    Multilingual Support: Available in Korean, English, Japanese, Chinese, Vietnamese, and more—perfect for users from different countries.</p><p>⸻</p><p>🎯 Use Cases<br>    •    Get Design Inspiration: Explore a variety of WordPress site styles to spark your design creativity.<br>    •    Reference for Portfolios: Check out site structures and features before starting your own WordPress project.<br>    •    Client Proposals: Use it to showcase different WordPress site examples when discussing style preferences with clients.</p><p>⸻</p><p>🔗 Visit Now</p><p>Click the link below to try WP-Viewer:</p><p>👉 <a href="http://www.wp-viewer.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://www.wp-viewer.com</a></p><p>For the English version, visit: <a href="http://www.wp-viewer.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://www.wp-viewer.com/</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/wordpress-wp-viewer/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eSender - Virtual Phone Number SMS Service</title>
      <link>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/esender-virtual-phone-number-sms-service/</link>
      <guid>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/esender-virtual-phone-number-sms-service/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        eSender - Virtual Phone Number SMS Service
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>eSender is a virtual phone number service that provides Chinese and Hong Kong phone numbers through WeChat. Here are the key points about eSender:</p><ul><li><strong>eSender</strong> : <a href="https://www.esenderchina.com/" target="_blank"><strong>www.esenderchina.com</strong></a></li></ul><h2 id="1-Purpose"><a href="#1-Purpose" class="headerlink" title="1. Purpose:"></a>1. Purpose:</h2><ul><li>It allows users to receive SMS verification codes and messages from Chinese/Hong Kong services without needing a physical SIM card</li><li>Particularly useful for people who need to register for Chinese services (like financial services, e-shopping, etc.) that require a Chinese phone number for verification</li></ul><h2 id="2-Key-Features"><a href="#2-Key-Features" class="headerlink" title="2. Key Features:"></a>2. Key Features:</h2><ul><li>Works through WeChat official account</li><li>Provides virtual phone numbers for both China and Hong Kong</li><li>Allows unlimited SMS reception</li><li>No need to change physical SIM cards</li><li>Supports sending SMS for registration on Chinese websites</li><li>Real-name registration is required (following telecom regulations)</li></ul><h2 id="3-How-it-works"><a href="#3-How-it-works" class="headerlink" title="3. How it works:"></a>3. How it works:</h2><ul><li>Users follow the eSender WeChat official account</li><li>Register with required information (including passport details for real-name verification)</li><li>Receive a virtual phone number</li><li>Can receive SMS messages directly through WeChat</li></ul><h2 id="4-Pricing"><a href="#4-Pricing" class="headerlink" title="4. Pricing:"></a>4. Pricing:</h2><ul><li>Offers various subscription periods (30 days, 90 days, 180 days, 360 days)</li><li>China number prices start from 28 HKD (approximately 3.60 USD) for 30 days</li><li>Hong Kong number prices start from 18 HKD (approximately 2.30 USD) for 30 days</li></ul><p>eSender is particularly useful for international users who need to access Chinese services that require local phone numbers for verification purposes, without having to physically obtain a Chinese SIM card.</p><ul><li><strong>eSender</strong> : <a href="https://www.esenderchina.com/" target="_blank"><strong>www.esenderchina.com</strong></a></li></ul>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/en/esender-virtual-phone-number-sms-service/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
