<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>MoneySkillTalk Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="/rss2.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    
    <description>Learn how to make the most of your money skill here.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 10:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    <generator>http://hexo.io/</generator>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Sites Random Viewer - Explore WordPress-built websites from around the world</title>
      <link>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/wordpress-wp-viewer/</link>
      <guid>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/wordpress-wp-viewer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        WordPress Sites Random Viewer is a web-based tool that allows you to explore WordPress-built websites from around the world at random.
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WordPress Sites Random Viewer (<a href="http://www.wp-viewer.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.wp-viewer.com</a>) is a web-based tool that allows you to explore WordPress-built websites from around the world at random. It’s a valuable resource for designers, developers, and marketers who want to quickly browse a wide range of WordPress site examples.</p><p>⸻</p><p>🔍 Key Features<br>    •    Random Site Browsing: Simply click the “Next” button to discover various WordPress websites randomly.<br>    •    Simple Interface: With just a click, you can browse new sites without any complicated setup, making it very user-friendly.<br>    •    Multilingual Support: Available in Korean, English, Japanese, Chinese, Vietnamese, and more—perfect for users from different countries.</p><p>⸻</p><p>🎯 Use Cases<br>    •    Get Design Inspiration: Explore a variety of WordPress site styles to spark your design creativity.<br>    •    Reference for Portfolios: Check out site structures and features before starting your own WordPress project.<br>    •    Client Proposals: Use it to showcase different WordPress site examples when discussing style preferences with clients.</p><p>⸻</p><p>🔗 Visit Now</p><p>Click the link below to try WP-Viewer:</p><p>👉 <a href="http://www.wp-viewer.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://www.wp-viewer.com</a></p><p>For the English version, visit: <a href="http://www.wp-viewer.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">http://www.wp-viewer.com/</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/wordpress-wp-viewer/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Analytics - Check whether a website is built with WordPress and various information</title>
      <link>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/wordpress-wp-data-analytics/</link>
      <guid>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/wordpress-wp-data-analytics/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        WordPress Analytics is a free online tool that checks whether a website is built with WordPress and analyzes information such as the theme, plugins, and hosting service being used.
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WordPress Analytics (<a href="http://www.wp-data.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.wp-data.com</a>) is a free online tool that checks whether a website is built with WordPress and analyzes information such as the theme, plugins, and hosting service being used. It is especially useful for developers, designers, and marketers who want to understand the technology stack of competitors or reference websites.</p><p>🔍 Main Features<br>    1.    WordPress Detection<br>• Automatically detects if the entered URL is a WordPress website.<br>    2.    Theme &amp; Plugin Analysis<br>• Identifies and lists the WordPress themes and plugins used on the site.<br>    3.    Hosting Service Information<br>• Estimates and displays the site’s hosting provider.<br>    4.    Agency Info Registration<br>• Allows users to add or edit agency information shown in the analysis.<br>    5.    Multilingual Support<br>• Available in multiple languages including Korean, English, Japanese, Chinese, and Vietnamese.</p><p>🛠 How to Use<br>    1.    Visit <a href="http://www.wp-data.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.wp-data.com</a><br>    2.    Enter the URL of the website you want to analyze (e.g., <a href="https://example.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://example.com</a>)    3.    Click the “Analyze” button to view information such as WordPress usage, theme, plugins, and hosting.</p><p>🎯 Use Cases<br>• Understand the tech stack of reference sites and apply it to your own projects.<br>• Benchmark competitors by checking which themes and plugins they use.<br>• Manage your agency portfolio by registering your agency’s information.</p><p>WordPress Analytics (<a href="http://www.wp-data.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">www.wp-data.com</a>) is a simple and convenient tool that requires no installation or login. It is highly useful for quickly retrieving technical information about WordPress-based websites. However, since it is based on publicly available data, some plugins or customized elements may not be detected accurately.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/wordpress-wp-data-analytics/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Sale Now - Get the latest discounts and free promotions for WordPress themes, plugins, and hosting services</title>
      <link>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/wordpress-wp-sale-now/</link>
      <guid>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/wordpress-wp-sale-now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        WordPress Sale Now is a website that provides real-time updates on the latest discounts and free promotions for WordPress themes, plugins, and hosting services.
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WordPress Sale Now is a website that provides real-time updates on the latest discounts and free promotions for WordPress themes, plugins, and hosting services. It’s a useful platform for those building or running websites or online stores, as it allows users to quickly view a wide range of deals all in one place.</p><p>⸻</p><p>🔍 Key Features<br>    1.    Real-Time Discount Updates<br>WordPress Sale Now constantly updates information on discounted themes, plugins, and hosting services, helping users find active promotions and purchase items at lower prices.<br>    2.    Free Download Promotions<br>Some premium themes and plugins are offered for free for a limited time. These promotions help users save costs while still accessing high-quality WordPress items.<br>    3.    Popular Product Rankings<br>The site provides weekly rankings of the most popular themes and plugins, helping users choose items that are currently trending and widely used.<br>    4.    Multilingual Support<br>WordPress Sale Now supports multiple languages including Korean, English, Japanese, and Chinese, making it accessible to users worldwide.</p><p>⸻</p><p>🛍️ Sample Discounted Products<br>    •    The7 Theme: A versatile theme with various design and layout options, currently available at 40% off.<br>    •    Elementor Plugin: A drag-and-drop page builder plugin, now offered at a 10% discount.<br>    •    Bluehost Hosting: A hosting service optimized for WordPress with various promotions currently available.</p><p>⸻</p><p>✅ Tips for Use<br>    •    Check Regularly: As discounts and free promotions are time-limited, visit the site frequently to stay up to date.</p><p>⸻</p><p>WordPress Sale Now is a convenient platform that gathers and shares discounts for WordPress-related products. It’s especially useful for those running websites or online businesses—feel free to check it out!</p><h1 id="Visit-now-https-www-wpsalenow-com"><a href="#Visit-now-https-www-wpsalenow-com" class="headerlink" title="Visit now: https://www.wpsalenow.com/"></a>Visit now: <a href="https://www.wpsalenow.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://www.wpsalenow.com/</a></h1>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/wordpress-wp-sale-now/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eSender - Virtual Phone Number SMS Service</title>
      <link>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/esender-virtual-phone-number-sms-service/</link>
      <guid>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/esender-virtual-phone-number-sms-service/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>
      
        eSender - Virtual Phone Number SMS Service
      
      </description>
      
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>eSender is a virtual phone number service that provides Chinese and Hong Kong phone numbers through WeChat. Here are the key points about eSender:</p><ul><li><strong>eSender</strong> : <a href="https://www.esenderchina.com/" target="_blank"><strong>www.esenderchina.com</strong></a></li></ul><h2 id="1-Purpose"><a href="#1-Purpose" class="headerlink" title="1. Purpose:"></a>1. Purpose:</h2><ul><li>It allows users to receive SMS verification codes and messages from Chinese/Hong Kong services without needing a physical SIM card</li><li>Particularly useful for people who need to register for Chinese services (like financial services, e-shopping, etc.) that require a Chinese phone number for verification</li></ul><h2 id="2-Key-Features"><a href="#2-Key-Features" class="headerlink" title="2. Key Features:"></a>2. Key Features:</h2><ul><li>Works through WeChat official account</li><li>Provides virtual phone numbers for both China and Hong Kong</li><li>Allows unlimited SMS reception</li><li>No need to change physical SIM cards</li><li>Supports sending SMS for registration on Chinese websites</li><li>Real-name registration is required (following telecom regulations)</li></ul><h2 id="3-How-it-works"><a href="#3-How-it-works" class="headerlink" title="3. How it works:"></a>3. How it works:</h2><ul><li>Users follow the eSender WeChat official account</li><li>Register with required information (including passport details for real-name verification)</li><li>Receive a virtual phone number</li><li>Can receive SMS messages directly through WeChat</li></ul><h2 id="4-Pricing"><a href="#4-Pricing" class="headerlink" title="4. Pricing:"></a>4. Pricing:</h2><ul><li>Offers various subscription periods (30 days, 90 days, 180 days, 360 days)</li><li>China number prices start from 28 HKD (approximately 3.60 USD) for 30 days</li><li>Hong Kong number prices start from 18 HKD (approximately 2.30 USD) for 30 days</li></ul><p>eSender is particularly useful for international users who need to access Chinese services that require local phone numbers for verification purposes, without having to physically obtain a Chinese SIM card.</p><ul><li><strong>eSender</strong> : <a href="https://www.esenderchina.com/" target="_blank"><strong>www.esenderchina.com</strong></a></li></ul>]]></content:encoded>
      
      <comments>https://blog.moneyskilltalk.com/esender-virtual-phone-number-sms-service/#disqus_thread</comments>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
